obdii365.com 2019-12-28

# Privacy Policy

* * *

## **Welcome to Obdii365.com. We respect your privacy very much, we will take your online safeguard seriously. To protect your privacy better, here are the details for you :**  

**The Information You Offer**  

For provide your with efficient customer service and quality products, when you register www.obdii365.com ,we will ask you about your personal information which includes Email, Name, Company Name, Street Address, Post Code, City, Country, Telephone Number, Password. So when if you could register and sign in successfully, we can recognize you and serve you for your need and make you have a much more delighted shopping experience on obdii365.com. Please make sure you offer your information completely and correctly. We promise that your personal information and your cookies will not be revealed to anyone on the internet or in any other ways.

**The Information We Use**

Internal Use: We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. Communication with You: We will use your personal information to communicate with you about Obdii365.com and your orders. You can unsubscribe or opt out of future emails at any time.You may also submit your email address to request notification when we receive a new brand, new product style or new released product, or to sign up for our email newsletter and special offers.

**Safeguard Your Information**  

As we respect your privacy very much, we safeguard your information seriously. Granting only employees who are providing a specific service access to your personal information. All employees that we do hire have to sign a confidentiality agreement that forbids them from disclosing any information to which the employee has access, to other individuals or entities. We employ the latest firewall protection to prevent unauthorized access into our information storage areas.We use the latest in encryption technology to ensure that any sensitive information. We also have back up servers and power supplies to guard against power outages and other natural occurrences that could pose a threat to the integrity of your personal information. Passwords are required in order for you to gain access to your account.  

**Choices for Your Information**

We usually offer you choices for your information. You can correct or update your personal information. You also can removing any information from your account which you that should be kept as private information. But please pay attention to that removing certain information such as your email address, contact information, and the like may greatly hinder our ability to offer the service or products you have requested effectively. Or you can contact us first to discuss the information that you would like to remove without interrupting the quality of service we intend to provide for you.

**Access to Your Information**

We do not sell, rent, trade, license, or otherwise disclose your personal or financial information to anyone, Only those employees who are responsible for handling your account have access to your information. In addition, employees in our technical department may have access to your information so that they can conduct routine checks on the integrity of our system and perform necessary maintenance work.

**Notice for Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. However, if any changes do occur that we will make the changes public and then post a notice on our site timely. We will also contact you personally to make you know of the new changes.

**Update of Policy**

For keeping you informed of what information we collect, use, and disclose, we will post any updates to this Privacy Notice on this site. So we recommend you to pay attention to this privacy policy occasionally.

Thanks in advance for your support!  
OBDII365 Team
